manulife iphones offers a wide array of
investment opportunities
that are tailor fit to your needs
here's how you can subscribe to fonts
go to the manulife iphones page to login
if you have forgotten your password you
can reset it
via email or by calling our customer
service
after logging in click on the menu
button
and select transact if you have multiple
accounts
choose which account you'd like to make
a transaction on
click on the subscription option to
explore
our range of funds select the fund
you want to invest in and if applicable
a currency class to view the funds
details and documents
set an investment amount a notification
will appear
if it is less than the fund's
requirement
please ensure you have read the offering
documents
and fully understood its contents by
checking the box
if you have not read the offering
documents please return to the previous
page
you can invest in multiple funds in one
transaction
but for this example we will only invest
in one fund
review your investment details and click
next
if your portfolio risk is higher than
the suggested score
of your risk profile a notice will
appear
giving you the options to confirm or
adjust your investments
read and acknowledge before clicking
confirm
review your investment details and make
payments
using your choice of method internet
banking fpx
or telegraphic transfer for
internet banking fpx you can only pay up
to thirty thousand malaysian ringgit
read and acknowledge the important notes
disclaimers
notices declaration and acceptance
and terms and conditions enter
the one-time password sent to your
mobile for verification
you will see a confirmation that your
application is received
and being processed you will also
receive an email confirmation
it's that easy to learn more reach out
to your manulife
investment management advisor or contact
our customer service now
at zero three two seven one nine nine
two
seven one
you